# HARRY WADA

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## INFO

#### **ADDRESS**

750 Synergy Park Blvd #12-238 Richardson TX, 75080

#### **PHONE**

(512) 703-7483

#### **EMAIL**

spam@harrywada.com

#### PLACE OF BIRTH

Carrollton, TX

#### **DRIVERS LICENSE**

None

#### **NATIONALITY**

American

#### LINKS

## Github

LinkedIn

Website

#### **SKILLS**

Go

С

React

Javascript

Linux

Docker

Git

Jira

## **PROFILE**

Emerging from the Austin Coding Academy as a front-end developer, my experience has since broadened to more general software as well. More than anything, I am an avid minimalist who believes in the prioritization of maintainability and documentability.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Software Engineer Intern, Bazaarvoice

Remote

May 2021 - August 2021

Was responsible for improving the Curalate service—a broad platform enabling brands to connect with shoppers and provide a more authentic shopping experience by relying on user-contributed media from social networking sites, among other features.

- Extended, improved, and bug-fixed various API services, and in doing so gained a comprehensive understanding of the microservice architecture
- · Made significant contributions to the open-source project twitter4s
- · Engaged in daily standup meetings and worked closely with other engineers

#### Software Engineer Intern, Bazaarvoice

Remote

May 2020 - August 2020

Engineered a solution to migrate data from production DynamoDB tables to newly managed PostgreSQL instances.

- · Migrated existing NoSQL data into a relational format using a custom Python script
- Developed and deployed infrastructure using Cloudformation templates

### Software Engineer Intern, Bazaarvoice

Austin, TX

May 2019 - November 2019

Developed a full-featured internal tool using React and Redux, easing the amount of effort required to accomplish the everyday processes of many teams.

- Worked with authenticated APIs to retrieve, create, and update data.
- Adopted an agile workflow in which constraints and requirements could change often and needed to be responded to in a timely manner

#### Software Developer Intern, Hunt Gather

Austin, TX

June 2017 - August 2017

Spent a summer working intimately with a small team of designers to prototype and develop a range of web apps and static websites.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Texas at Dallas, B.S. in Computer Science May 2023

# **Austin Coding Academy, Graduation from Advanced Class**

September 2016